What if every moment in life came with a second chance?
About Time is a drama, romance, fantasy film directed by Richard Curtis.
The night after another unsatisfactory New Year's party, Tim's father tells his son that
the men in his family have always had the ability to travel through time.
They can't change history, but they can change what
happens and has happened in their own lives.
Thus begins the start of a lesson in learning to appreciate life itself as it is,
as it comes, and most importantly, the people living alongside us.
Tim Lake, played by Domhnall Gleeson.
Mary, played by Rachel McAdams.
Dad, played by Bill Nighy.
Harry, played by Tom Hollander.
Charlotte, played by Margot Robbie.
Kit Kat, played by Lydia Wilson.
About Time is a 2013 romantic science fiction comedy-drama film written and directed by
Richard Curtis, and starring Domhnall Gleeson, Rachel McAdams, and Bill Nighy.
The film is about a young man with the ability to time travel who tries
to change his past in hopes of improving his future.
The film was released in the United Kingdom on 4 September 2013.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
At the box office, it grossed $87.1 million against a $12 million budget.
It was dedicated to actor Richard Griffiths, who died a few months before
the film's release, marking his final film appearance.
The film explores themes of london, england, soulmates, parent
child relationship, time travel, family secrets.
The tone is lighthearted and uplifting and emotional.